本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧字幕 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：老奶奶      校对：小路     时间轴：虫不知
特效：Will      后期：冰河       监制：蛐蛐
■
绝
命
毒
师
第二季
第二集
好了  大家听着
All right, everybody.Listen up.
屠库·塞拉曼加
Tuco Salamanca.
你们有些人今早没跟我们一起
For those of you not with us this morning,
我们抄了他的老窝
We raided his headquarters.
同时掌握了他最后的地址
Also his last known address.
还有他留给他毒枭女友的非法藏匿地
Even the little den of iniquity he keeps for his meth hag girlfriend.
我们抓捕了一批他的马仔
We netted a bunch of his lieutenants.
他则预料到了我们的出现
The big man himself smelled us coming.
所以
So...
认清这张脸
Study the face.
弄清档案
Study the file.
性趣盎然地
Get a big ol'raging hard on
准备抓到这个垃圾
At the idea of catching this piece of shit.
我向人力资源部的同事道歉
My apologies to the HR department.
应该是满怀憧憬的
Grow tumescent with anticipation.
在本地帮派正和摩托党抢毒品生意时
On the hit parade, 1998.
因暴打疯狗保尔森而扬名天下
Reputed to have whacked "Dog" Paulson,back when our home-grown banditos
而荣登98年的恶人排行榜
Where wrestling the crank trade away from the So Cal biker gangs.
此外  03年我们确信他曾捅死过一个墨西哥人
Also, we're pretty sure he knifed a Mexican national in '03.
依我看来  以他对待死对头的一贯做法
And for my money, seeing how he customarily deals with rivals,
不得不说我们日思夜想的疯狂小八的失踪
I'd say he is a prime suspect
应该跟他有极大的关系
In the disappearance of our dearly-missed Krazy-8.
大家尽全力抓住那个混球
Hats over your heart for that dirtball.
我们曾经抓屠库进来查问过这件事
We hauled Tuco in for questioning on that one,
老样子  还是没什么确凿证据
But as usual,we couldn't make it stick.
这个自以为是的混蛋做事很谨慎
He runs a tight ship.Smug bastard.
更糟的是  埃尔帕索说他跟大毒品集团有往来
And even worse, El Paso says he's got some kind of cartel connection.
我们都清楚这件事的后果会怎样
I know it's...We all know what's going on down there.
我们也不希望自己出什么岔子
We sure as hell don't want it going on up here.
好消息来了
Which brings us to the good news.
我们终于掌握了一些确凿的证据
We finally got some actual,honest-to-God evidence.
这是屠库手下  绰号"不瞌睡"
This is one of Tuco's henchmen.Street name, No Doze.
在垃圾场发现他的尸体  还有屠库妹夫
Found him tucked in the junkyard,along with Tuco's own brother-in-law,
绰号怪诞
A.K.A. Gonzo.
怪诞  这个万事通  正在处理"不瞌睡"的尸体
Gonzo, this rocket scientist,was moving No Doze's body,
还不确定他是扔到那里还是从那里往外运
Either hiding it there or pulling it out, still not sure,
他的胳膊被砸烂了
When he got his arm crushed clean off.
想看那些照片的  我网站上有  很有趣
Anyone wanna see the photos,they're on my Web site. Hilarious.
总之  结果就是
Anyway. The upshot is,
我们得到一个漂亮  大号  多汁  血淋淋的指纹
We got us a nice,big, juicy, bloody fingerprint,
指纹的主人是屠库
Which belongs to senor Tuco.
我们的圣诞节提前到来了
Christmas came early to the Schrader household.
不过我们得先找到这家伙
That is, provided we find this guy.
在座的各位
So to all present,
你们想找到这家伙吗
I ask you, you wanna find this guy?
你们刚刚说什么
What the hell was that? Jesus.
要再来一次吗
Wanna try that again?
你们想找到这家伙吗
Do you want to find this guy?
我们会找到这家伙吗
Are we going to find this guy?
大声点  该死
Louder, damn it!
-大家一起哦耶  -哦耶
- Give me a hell, yeah!  - Hell, yeah!
他们找不到他的
They ain't gonna find him.
那家伙正在墨西哥呢
Guy's in Mexico by now.
面子  格米  这都是为了面子
Appearances, Gomie.It's all about appearances.
听着  我有点私事要处理
Listen,I gotta take some personal time.
现在吗  追捕正进行着呢
Now, in the middle of a manhunt?
斯凯勒昨晚打电话  说沃尔特不见了
Skyler called last night.It's Walt.He's missing.
突然从家里消失  之后便杳无音信
Just disappeared from the house,and no one's heard from him since.
该死  你不会认为他
Damn. You don't think he...
-有事叫我  -谢谢  感激不尽
- Holler if you need me.  - Thanks a lot, man. Appreciate that.
这是最近的一张  很久没拍照片了  所以
This is the most recent photo.We haven't taken many lately, so...
现在还是那个样子
But that's what he looks like now.
只不过没有头发
Without the hair.
是我
Hey, it's me.
提姆  感谢你放假时间还过来
Hey, Tim. Really appreciate you sparing us your day off.
没关系  很乐意帮忙
No worries. Happy to help.
这个很有帮助  很好
Yeah, this is helpful. Good.
-身高体重呢  -五尺十一寸
- What about height and weight?  - Five eleven...
最近称170磅
Most recently, about 170.
我体重是165磅
165. That's what I weigh.
我猜
I guess...
-他会轻一点  -没关系  差不多
- He weighs a little less.  - That's fine. That's close enough.
很好
Good.
还有其他什么特征码
What about other distinguishing features?
纹身  痣或者伤疤
Tattoos or moles or scars?
-任何信息都有帮助  -纹身
- Anything that might help us...  - Tattoos?
没有
Not really.
没关系
That's fine.
-那是他用药的清单吗  -是的  我都写下来了
- Is that the list of medications?  - Yes. I wrote them all down.
没有药物的相互反应  单子上的没有
And there's no drug interactions.None that are listed.
我打过电话给他医生  没有的
I called his doctor, so, no.
他最近抑郁吗
Has he been depressed?
他最近有点孤僻  一点点
He's been withdrawn lately.A little withdrawn.
昨晚  他
Last night, he was...
烦躁
Agitated.
是的  昨晚他回来的时候  他
Yeah. When he came home last night,he was...
烦躁  不高兴
Agitated, upset.
周期性不高兴  还是因为什么事情不高兴
Upset in general? Or upset because of something particular?
我问他出什么事  他说
When I asked him what was wrong,he said...
我不知道从何开始
"I don't know where to begin."
然后他就走出了浴室
Then he just walked out of the bathroom...
我当时在浴缸洗澡呢
I was in the tub. Taking a bath.
我十分钟之后出来时  他就不见了
And when I came out about ten minutes later, he was gone.
丢什么东西没
Nothing else missing?
他的钥匙  钱包  手机  就这些随身物品
His keys, wallet, cell phone.Just what was on him.
那个电话呢
What about the phone call?
我正查呢
I'm looking into it.
什么电话
What phone call?
沃尔特电话响过  他拿出来
Walt's cell phone rang.He pulled it out,
看了一下  但是没有接
Looked at it, and didn't answer it.
之后一会儿他便出了浴室
But then, a short time after,he wandered out of the bathroom.
我是说
I mean...
那个会不会是
Couldn't that be...
重要线索  对吗
Important, right?
你还记得什么事情
Anything else you can think of?
其他事情
Anything else.
我打电话给信用卡提供商
I called the credit card providers,
最近没有使用记录
And there's no report of any recent activity.
我查问了方圆50里之内的每家医院
Let's see...I checked with every hospital within 50 miles.
每个警局  每个停尸房
Every police station. Every morgue.
没有  没有其他什么信息了
So, no, I really don't...I don't have anything else.
我倒希望你们有其他什么信息
I was actually hoping that you had something else,
毕竟你们是专业的
Being that you're the expert.
-对不起  -别担心
- I'm sorry.  - No worries.
这是个很好的开端
I think this is good enough to start.
我们有许多工作要做
Gives us plenty to work on.
-哈特维尔夫人  -谢谢
- Mrs.Hartwell  - Thank you.
-沃尔特  -谢谢
- Walter.  - Thank you
她提到的那个电话  我查过了
So that cell phone call she's talking about? I ran it.
-然后呢  -根本就没有打过  没有记录
- And?  - Never happened. No record of it.
-他还有一部电话  -是的  我也这么想
- Second cell phone.  - Yeah. I'm thinking...
我明白
I understand.
出来
Out!
放开我
Get away from me!
安静点  疯狗
Settle down, bitch!
你要开枪打我吗
You gonna shoot me?
放马过来吧
Shoot me in here!
我倒是希望放点血啊
I hope I bleed like a mother, too!
那样的话  你就有得打扫了
That way, you have to clean it up!
弱智  这是你的车  我才不用收拾  出来
It's your ride, retard.I ain't gotta clean jack. Now get out!
起来
Get up!
Get up.
屠库  不要这样
Don't do this, Tuco.
没有寻人启事了
No more posters?
小沃尔特正在做呢
Walter Junior's making more.
玛丽  谢谢你
Thank you, Marie.
我不认为他会自杀
I don't think he'll hurt himself.
印象中他不是这样的人
I mean, he just doesn't strike me as the type.
他会回头的
He'll turn up.
好吧  整个头冠这件事
Okay, the whole tiara thing...
我觉得有些令人费解
I just find it bewildering that...
你竟然不相信
You didn't believe that...
现在不是时候
Not now.
兜儿里东西都掏出来
Empty your pockets.
我还以为你叫海森堡呢
Thought your name was Heisenberg,
沃尔特·哈特维尔·怀特
"Walter Hartwell White."
海森堡是个假名
Heisenberg is kind of a pseudonym.
交易用的名字
A business name.
我就喜欢跟有家室的人做交易
I like doing business with a family man.
总会有许多抵押品
There's always a lot of collateral.
回答我一个问题
Answer me one thing.
我能相信你吗
Can I trust you?
是的  当然可以
Yes, absolutely.
坐下
Sit down.
缉毒局
DEA...
今早抄了我的老窝
Hit my place of business this morning.
一百来个条子来抓我
About a hundred cops looking for me.
你们俩还没去谈过话吧
You two haven't been talking, right?
我从上到下的兄弟都被抓了
Picked up my whole crew,top to bottom.
除了怪诞
Everybody except Gonzo.
很奇怪吧
That's weird, right?
我是说
I mean,
你们不觉得很奇怪吗
Don't you think that that's weird?
没错  很奇怪
That's weird. Yes.
不正常
Unusual.
前两天
Last two days,
我电话联系不到怪诞
I couldn't get Gonzo on the phone.
因为"不瞌睡"他一直很易怒
He's been acting all pouty on account of No Doze.
解释一下
Explain to me,
现在那个混蛋不知所踪
How is it my fault
这是我的错吗
That that little bitch did not know his place?
我早就料到
I saw this coming.
我可以预测未来
I can see the future, you know?
我有个天赋
It's this gift that I have
就是过目不忘
Deep inside my head.
昨晚我就知道他们会来抓我
I knew last night they were going to come and try and bust me.
怪诞  他给条子通风报信了
Gonzo...He went and snitched to the cops!
那个无耻的混球
That lousy son of a bitch!
我如兄弟一般信任他
I trusted him like a brother!
我待他不薄  不薄啊
I was good to him!I was good!
看到他  我非剁了他不可
I see Gonzo, I'm going to cut him,
扒了他的皮
I'm going to skin him,
把他装进袋子里天天打
And I'm going to stuff his hide for a heavy bag,
每打他一次
And every time I hit him,
我就吸取一次教训
It's going to be like a lesson to myself!
永远不要相信你爱的人
You never,never trust the people that you love!
你打算干掉怪诞
So, you plan to ice Gonzo,
在不久的将来
Like, future tense?
你在说
You're saying...
You're saying that...
目前怪诞
Gonzo is currently...
据你所知  他是警方的线人
Operating as a police informant,as far as you know?
很遗憾听到这个消息
I'm very sorry to hear that.
太令人失望了
That's disappointing.
-要是我  我也会废了他的  -闭嘴
- I'd waste him, too, yo.  - Shut up.
条子正满世界找我呢
They're out there looking for me right now.
他们动用了警用直升机还有特别行动小组
They got ghetto birds and black ops.
我得来点刺激的
I need to get high.
好好的爽一下
I need to get good and high.
这是什么玩意  闻起来想猪头冻
What's with this gak? It smells like headcheese.
这是猛料
It's killer.
是的  说真的
Yeah, seriously.
昨晚我考虑了一下
So, I was thinking last night.
想出了这个绝妙的主意
I came up with this great idea.
墨西哥
Mexico.
Mexico?
我们消失在茫茫的丛林之中
We'll disappear way out in the jungle.
给你们配备一个超级实验室
We'll set you up in a superlab.
一刻不停地制毒
We'll do nothing but cook 24-7.
联邦警察可管不了我们
And no federales are going to mess with us,
因为那里有我的人
Because I got my people there.
关系
Connections.
我们将会
We're going to make
大赚特赚  海森堡
beaucoup bucks, Heisenberg.
我有妻子和家庭
I have a wife and family.
那又怎样  再找一个
So what? You'll get another one.
我不想让你误会
I don't want you to take this the wrong way,
但是我不能
But I can't just...
就这么毁了我的家庭
Uproot my life like that.
是的 我也不能
Yeah, man.I mean, me, neither.
谁问你话了吗
Who's talking to you?
你需要我
You need me, man,
你手里那个猛料可是我做出来的
'cause I cooked that scante in your hands.
老实跟你说吧
I'll tell you something, yo.
你肯定没尝过这种货
You never tried nothing like it.
无论气味如何
Stink or no stink,
一口下去
One bump,
接下来的几天你都飘飘欲仙
You'll be flying high for days.
这是我俩研制出来的新品
It's a new product him and I been working up.
嗑的时候悠着点
Careful when you hit it.
劲儿上来跟开12-guage一样爽[12-guage 一种12毫米重机枪]
It kicks like a 12-gauge when it comes on.
这可是独家配料
It's got a secret ingredient.
什么独家配料
What secret ingredient?
辣椒粉
Chili powder.
我讨厌辣椒粉
I hate chili powder.
这个蓝精灵  这才值钱
This blue magic, this is money.
海森堡  你继续制这个
You keep cooking this, Heisenberg.
我们就用这个改写历史吧
We're going to rewrite history with this.
好了
All right!
是时候干掉这个小鬼头了  省的心烦
Time to clean the menudo out from between your ears!
不  我需要他  屠库
No, I need him, Tuco.
我非常非常需要他
I need him very, very badly.
他是我的搭档
He's my partner.
如果他去不了
And if he doesn't go,
我也不去
I don't go.
告诉你吧  我堂兄正开车赶过来
I'll tell you this,my cousins are driving up here
把我们偷渡过去
Right now to smuggle us back down,
他们天黑前就到
And they're going to be here by sunset,
要么我们一起走
And you're going to be on that truck,
要么你就等死吧
Or you're going to be dead!
你呢
And you...
你最好祈祷车上还有空座
You better hope they got room in the trunk.
你去哪儿
Where are you going?
路易斯要带我去火车站
Louis is taking me to the train station.
我们去贴这些东西
We'll put these on.
不用了  亲爱的  我去贴吧
No, no, honey.No, I'll do it.
他想要帮忙  就让他帮忙吧
He wants to help, let him help.
你有多久没睡觉了
I mean, how long has it been since you've slept?
她说的没错  斯凯  你去躺一下吧
Yeah, she's right,Sky.Why don't you lay down a while?
况且你还怀着小宝宝呢
For Christ sake,you got a bun in the oven.
有事你就打我的手机
I got my cell if you need me.
再见  宝贝  待会儿见
Bye, sweetie.I'll see you later.
好的  再见
All right. Bye.
事实上
Actually,
目前为止还没有找到他
I think the very fact they haven't found him yet...
或许是个好消息
bodes well.
我是说  如果他
Well, I mean, if he...
你知道
You know.
肯定会有人发现些什么的
Somebody would've smelled something by now.
一定还有些事情
There's got to be something,
一些我们没有注意到的细节
Some detail that we haven't picked up on.
第二部手机有什么线索
What about the second cell phone?
天呐
Aw, Jesus.
怎么了  任何线索都不能放过的  汉克
What? We can't just ignore a potential clue, Hank.
好了  你们在说什么
Okay. What are you talking about?
沃尔特失踪前接到的那个电话
The call you said Walt got before he disappeared,
电话公司并没有任何记录
There's no record of it with the phone company.
没有来电  也没有中断电话  什么都没有
No incoming,no dropped calls, nothing.
但是他电话响了  我听到了
But his phone rang.I heard it.
没错  问题就在这里
Well, all right.Well, then, if that's the case,
他肯定还有部手机
He must have a second phone.
为什么  他要两个手机干什么
Why? What sense would there be in that?
好吧  我不想跟你争执
All right. Okay. I'm not here to argue with you.
不  汉克  你不能就提一下那个神秘电话
No, Hank. You can't just bring up "secret cell phone"
那意味着什么
What does it mean?
我不知道  斯凯  你想要我说什么
I don't know, Sky. What do you want me to say?
说明沃尔特有自己的秘密
It means Walt has a secret.
人人都有秘密  或大或小
Everyone's got one from somebody,big or little.
人人
"Everyone."
他得癌症的消息还瞒了你很久呢
He kept cancer from you for weeks.
好吧  假设他还有一部手机
Then, let's assume there'a second cell phone.
怎么了  说明他有外遇了吗
So, what? Is he having an affair?
沃尔特  拜托
Walt? Please.
是不是他又吸大麻了
What about the marijuana?
他已经不吸那个了
He's not on pot anymore.
谁说的  他自己吗
Says who? Him?
化疗跟大麻如影相随
Chemotherapy and marijuana go together
就像苹果派和雪弗莱一样
Like apple pie and Chevrolet.
或许
Maybe...
他又上瘾了
He's addicted to the pot,
欠了毒贩子一大笔钱
And he owes his drug dealer a lot of money.
他不会这样的
You don't get hooked on pot like that.
你连他有两部电话都不知道
You didn't even know he had a second cell phone.
汉克  你得去问问那个毒贩子
Hank,you have to question this drug dealer person.
他或许知道些情况
He may know something.
告诉你吧  那可是我们的救命稻草
Well, I'm telling you,we're grasping at straws here.
那就抓稳了
Then grasp.
打扰一下  夫人
Excuse me. Ma'am?
我找杰西  他在吗
Hi. I'm looking for Jesse.He around?
不在
No. I'm afraid not.
-什么事  -抱歉  我是汉克·施拉德
- Why?  - I'm sorry. Hank Schrader.
我想跟杰西谈谈
I'm actually hoping to talk to Jesse
关于我姐夫沃尔特·怀特的事
About my brother-in-law, Walter White.
他是你儿子高中的化学老师
He taught your son chemistry in high school.
怀特先生啊  是的  我记得他
Oh, Mr. White.Yes, I remember him.
那是很久之前的事了
That was a long time ago.
是的  女士
Yes, ma'am.
我认为他和杰西
It's my understanding that he and Jesse,
一直都有联系
They've stayed in touch.
真的吗
Really?
怀特先生一定看中了杰西的一些潜质
Mr. White must've seen some potential in Jesse.
他一直试图激励他
He really tried to motivate him.
他是为数不多关心杰西的老师之一
He was one of the few teachers who cared.
是的  沃尔特就是那样  他是个好人
Yeah, Walt's that way.He's a good man.
很遗憾他得了这个病
I'm so sorry to hear about his illness.
请代我向他致以最美好的祝愿
Please pass along our best wishes.
等他回来之后  我一定会的
I certainly will,as soon as he turns up.
事实上  他失踪了
He's missing, actually.
像是出走或者
Just kind of walked off or...
总之  所以我才四处打听
Anyway, which is why I'm going around
认识他的人  虽然希望不大
Trying to think of anyone who knows him, even slightly.
太糟了
That's terrible.
我们能帮上什么忙吗
Anything we can do to help?
能帮我联系到你儿子吗
Well, if you could put me in touch with your son.
我说过了  实在没有什么线索了
Like I said, we're kind of desperate for leads.
我给杰西打电话  他都没接
Jesse's not answering either phone number I have for him,
也没有人见到他在家里
And no one seems to be home at his house.
你凭什么认为我儿子和怀特先生有联系
And why do you think my son and Mr. White would be in touch?
我也不确定  只是
I don't necessarily. I just...
-你是警察吗  -不  女士  我不是
- Are you with the police?  - No, ma'am. Not at all.
我是缉毒局的
I'm with the Drug Enforcement Administration.
天呐  我儿子惹什么事了吗
Oh, my God.Is my son in trouble?
我不认为这样
I have absolutely no reason to think that, no.
我需要请个律师吗
Do I need to get a lawyer?
你对这件事有点支支吾吾的
You know, you don't seem very forthright about this,
过来就问这问那的
Coming here and asking questions about my son...
平克曼女士  我向你发誓
Mrs. Pinkman, I swear to you,
我不是代表官方来这里
I'm not here on official capacity.
我不在乎你儿子是否做了什么坏事
I do not care what your son may or may not have done wrong.
我只想找到我姐夫
I just want to find my brother-in-law.
他妻子担心死了
His wife is worried sick,
而且正怀着身孕
And she's got a baby on the way.
抱歉  我很想帮你
I'm sorry.I would like to help you,
但我有一个多月没见着我儿子了
But I have not seen my son in over a month.
最近估计他也不会出现了
I don't expect to see him anytime soon.
感谢您的配合
Well, thanks for your time.
还有一个问题
If you could tell me one more thing.
据你所知
Is Jesse still driving the, uh,
杰西的车子是不是89款的雪佛兰蒙特卡洛
'89 Chevy Monte Carlo,as far as you know?
如果他能花一半时间和精力在学习上
If he had spent half as much time and money on his education
而不是捣鼓那辆无聊的弹簧车
As he has on that ridiculous bouncing car...
低底盘的
Lowrider, huh?
还没消息呢  听着  帮我查一下
Nah, nothing yet. Listen,do me a solid and check out a...
一款89款雪佛兰蒙特卡洛
'89 Chevy Monte Carlo
注册在杰西·平克曼名下
Registered to a one Jesse Pinkman.
尤其注意一下有没有装防盗追踪系统
Specifically? I want to know if the car's got LoJack.
是那种强力型低底盘的车子
It's one of those jackoff lowriders.
很有可能装了
It's got a good shot that there is.
如果有的话  立马帮我进行追踪  谢啦
If so, can you go ahead and get me a fix on it? Thanks, buddy.
辣椒粉
Chili powder.
我难道没告诉你那有多么低能吗
Did I not already tell you how moronic that was?
无所谓了
Whatever, man.
至少我尝试了
At least I tried something.
差点就成功了
It almost worked, too.
你还落下了我的枪呢
How's about you leaving my gun?
先是偷走了  然后又落在自己屋子里
First you boost it, then you leave it in your house.
我的枪
My gun.
我怎么会知道
How was I supposed to know
你要带着屠库来我这里
You were chauffeuring Tuco to my doorstep?
至少他要留你的活口
Well, at least he wants you alive.
我不明白了
Hey, I don't get it.
屠库没有杀死怪诞  那是谁干的呢
If Tuco didn't kill Gonzo,then who did?
不知道
I don't know.
这个很重要吗
Does it really matter?
如果他发现怪诞已经死了
If he finds out that Gonzo is dead
并且他不是警方的线人
And not a police informant,
他会怪罪谁呢
Who does he automatically blame?
我们
Us.
我们得计划一下
We need a plan.
好好想想
Think, think.
我们偷袭他吧
Let's just bum-rush him, man.
你拿东西砸他的脑袋
You know, you crack him over the head with something,
我去抢枪
And I'll go for his gun.
拿东西砸他脑袋
"Crack him over the head with something"?
反正你得了癌症
And you got the C-bomb, man.
早晚都是死
You're as good as checked out already.
你应该像个烈士一样
You should be, like,all sacrificial,
扑向手榴弹
Jumping on a grenade, yo.
就是说我的命不再重要了
Oh, so my life is not the priority here,
因为我离死不远了
Because I'm going to be dead soon anyway.
你是这么想的吗
That's your point?
我们得让他尝尝这个
We got to get him to take this.
他不喜欢辣椒粉的味道
He don't much like the taste of chili P.
这点他已经明确说明了
That much has been established.
除非你能说服他塞进屁眼里
So unless you can convince him to booty bump...
吃吧
Eat.
还有很长的路要赶呢
We've got a long ride ahead of us.
去坐下吧
Go and sit.
你看起来有点虚  海森堡
You're looking a little weak, Heisenberg.
我可不想还没到那儿你就挂了
I don't want you to go belly up before we get there.
别着急  迪奥
Take it easy, Tio.
我先吃  然后喂你
I will feed you. I eat first.
说好了的
That's the deal.
怎么了
What?
我明白了  明白了
I get it, I get it, I get it.
你这个贪婪的老混球
You greedy old bastard.
告诉你吧  海森堡
I tell you, Heisenberg...
老人
Old people.
你喂养他们
You feed them, huh?
即使把他们放在乡下的粮仓里
You put them in a really nice crib in the country,
他们还是会从你盘子里偷吃的
And yet they gotta steal the food off your plate.
你最好都吃完了
You better eat every bite of that.
你搞什么
What did you do that for?
天呐
God!
看啊
Look. Lookit.
一点都不剩
There's nothing left.
怎么
What?
你想怎样
What do you want?
别告诉我你饿了
Don't even tell me that you're hungry.
别给我来这一套
Don't go there.
你在向他们示威吗  迪奥
Are you mad-dogging them, Tio?
你不喜欢他们吗
What, you don't like them?
一声响  是肯定的回答
One ding. That means "yes."
迪奥不喜欢你们
Tio don't like you.
迪奥  你为什么不喜欢他们
Why don't you like them, Tio?
你不信任他们
You don't trust them?
为什么不信任他们呢  迪奥
Why don't you trust them, Tio?
屠库  拜托  我是说  他
Tuco, come on.I mean, he's...
他明显是个痴呆  脑子不好使
There's clearly some dementia.He's not lucid.
他们对你做什么了吗
Did they do something to you, Tio?
你不喜欢的事情
Something that you don't like?
他们对你做什么了
What did they do to you?
你们对我的迪奥做什么了
What did you do to my Tio?
没什么
Nothing.
放屁  我的迪奥不会撒谎的
Bullshit! My Tio does not lie!
我不知道  我发誓  我不知道
I don't know. I swear.I don't know.
或许  我确实换了频道  但是
Maybe, I did change the channel on his TV, but...
就这样  你做饭时  他正看电视呢
That's it.While you were cooking,he was watching one of those...
那个电视小说上有许多美女
Those "telenovels" with all those ripe honeys on it?
他看得很起劲  我告诉你不要换台的
He was really into it. I told you not to change the channel, man!
老家伙要过个眼瘾  就这样
Dude needs his eye candy. That's it.
是这样吗  迪奥
Is that it, Tio?
是不是他们换走了你的美女
Did they change your mamitas?
你想说什么  迪奥
What are you telling me, Tio?
他们是不是在耍我
Are they punking me?
不要
No, man.
过来
Come here!
闭嘴
Shut up!
不要
Please, no!
求你了  不要  我不想死
Please, no! No, God! I don't want to die!
沃尔特  你们到底做什么了
Tell me what you did, Walter!
天呐
Jesus!
我不想死
I don't want to die!
你们做什么了
Tell me what you did!
我们想给你下毒
We tried to poison you.
We tried to poison you,
因为你是个疯子
Because you're an insane,
一陀大便
Degenerate piece of filth,
死不足惜
And you deserve to die.
现在谁是二货啊
Who's the bitch now?
让他流血至死吧
Let him bleed.
钥匙呢
The keys!
天呐
Oh, my God.
他兄弟
The cousins?
怎么回事
What the hell's going on?
杰西·平克曼
Jesse Pinkman.
你还真的难找啊
You're a hard man to find.
该死
Aw, shit.
慢点
Easy.
天呐
Oh, my God.
-汉克  -谁
- Hank.  - Who?
-汉克  -什么
- Hank.  - What?
-天呐  -什么
- Oh, my God.  - What?
-天呐  -待着  你要干什么
- Oh, my God.  - Stay. What are you doing?